好
Okay.
准备来一个狼人的嚎叫吧  很关键哦
Get ready for a howl that is going to change your life.
好咧  准备好了
(Chuckles) Okay, get ready.
来了哦
It's coming. (Clears throat)
你知道的
Although, you know...
刚刚想了想
Just sort of like off the top of my head,
少点吼叫多点清脆怎么样
what if it was sort of less of a howl and more of a whistle?
嗯  嗯
Yeah, yeah.
我是说，观众完全
'Cause I mean, the audience totally...
嚎叫
just howl!
明白
Got it.
我叫“獠牙”·沃尔夫特  我是来这儿为的角色试镜的
My name is fangs wolfert, and I'm here to try out for the part of Tristan.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
给我一分钟时间和我的狼人教练私聊一会儿
Just give me one second to talk to my wolf coach real quick.
给我出去
Get out.
狼人想干就干
A wolf takes what it wants.
我要拿下这个角色
And I'm taking this part.
噢
Oh.
我们可是在舞台上哦  獠牙
We are on a soundstage right now, fangs.
我的底盘
This is my territory.
此言差矣
Doesn't look like it.
我是特里斯坦莱肯
I am Tristan Lycanth.
不  我才是特里斯坦莱肯
No, I am Tristan Lycanth.
结束
And scene.
哇哦
Wow.
我们讨论一下然后回来
Let us discuss and we'll get back to you.
查查是谁帮她做的头发
Find out who styles the brunette's hair.
简直是超爱
I love it.
獠牙
Fangs!
这都是我的计划
All part of my plan.
哦哦
Oh-ho...
真不赖
You are good.
我知道只要我向你挑战  咱们所有的努力都会有回报的
I knew that if I threatened your territory, all our hard work would pay off
而你的狼人本性就会显露无疑
and your inner wolf would emerge.
虽然不知道我有没有胜过莱恩·戈斯林和莱恩·戈斯林
Well, I don't know if I'd beat Gosling or diesel,
但是  我做到了獠牙  我吼出来了
but I did it, fangs. I howled.
是的
I heard.
听起来像我妈妈
It sounded like my mother.